Finding Aid for the John Cope Caldwell Papers MSS.0066
Vanderbilt University Special Collections
- Correspondence - Incoming (Box 4)
  - Regnery, Henry (70), 1952-1964
    Dates of letters: Mar. 11, 1952, Mar. 24, 1952, Apr. 1, 1952, Apr. 25, 1952, Apr. 30, 1952, May 1, 1952, May 16, 1952, May 20, 1952, May 26, 1952, June 2, 1952, Aug. 22, 1952, Sept. 24, 1952, Sept. 25, 1952, Oct. 4, 1952, Oct. 21, 1952, Oct. 23, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, Nov. 5, 1952, Nov. 28, 1952, Dec. 18, 1952, Dec. 29, 1952, Feb. 26, 1953, Apr. 16, 1953, June 2, 1953, July 20, 1953, Nov. 23, 195: Jan. 7, 1954, June 24, 1954, Aug. 4, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 26, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Sept. 23, 1954, Nov. 30, 1954, Dec. 27, 1954, Dec. 30, 1954, Jan. 6, 1955, Jan. 22, 1955, Feb. 17, 1955, Mar. 8, 1955, Mar. 10, 1955, Mar. 16, 1955, Apr. 4, 1955, May 6, 1955, July 17, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Sept. 7, 1956, Oct. 22, 1956, Dec. 6, 1956, Dec. 14, 1956, Jan. 7, 1957, Jan. 28, 1957, Feb. 1, 1957, Mar. 14, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 24, 1957, July 10, 1957, Aug. 9, 1957, Aug. 23, 1957, Dec. 3, 1957, Dec. 11, 1957, Jan. 3, 1958, Oct. 31, 1958, Nov. 12, 1958, Jan. 6, 1959, Jan. 27, 1959, Aug. 31, 1964, Sept. 10, 1964
  - Reidy, Loretta (25), 1951-1961
    Dates of letters: June 26, 1951, Aug. 17, 1951, Feb. 19, 1952, Feb. 25, 1952, Aug. 22, 1952, Oct. 7, 1952, Nov. 19, 1952, Dec. 9, 1952, Dec. 17, 1952, Jan. 12, 1953, Jan. 20, 1953, Mar. 25, 1953, Aug. 13, 1953, Jan. 22, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Mar. 3, 1954, Sept. 1, 1954, Oct. 12, 1954, Oct. 15, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954, Apr. 11, 1955, Sept. 26, 1955, Apr. 13, 1956, Dec. 17, 1959, Mar. 10, 1961
  - Reiff, Julie W. (2), Oct. 31, 1960, Nov. 27, 1960
  - Reinicke, F. G. (2), Nov. 20, 1957, Nov. 27, 1957
    8
  - Ribbe, Walter F. (1), May 3, 1954
  - Richards, Jack (1), Apr. 11, 1955
  - Richards, Sarra 0., (1), Nov. 25, 1959
  - Richmond, Brenda (1), Jan. 19, 1961
  - Richmond, Charlotte (10), Mar. 14, 1958, Mar. 31, 1958, Jan. 8, 1959, June 19, 1959, Aug. 21, 1959, Jan. 29, 1960, Aug. 12, Aug. 18, 1960, Sept. 12, 1960, Sept. 14, 1960
  - Rigby, Patricia, Ann (1), Feb. 27, 1964
  - Rikon, Charles (2), Feb. 13, 1959, Mar. 13, 1959
  - Riley, C. M. (1), Nov. 1, 1955
  - Roberts, Dave (1), Mar. 26, 1951
  - Robertson, Anna Douglas (1), May 20, 1953
  - Rodes, John B. (1), Mar. 18, 1955
  - Roerkohl, Marcelline E. (2), Apr. 3, 1963, Jan. 15, 1964
  - Rogers, George F. (1), Mar. 12, 1951
  - Ronnow, Joan (1), Mar. 11, 1966
  - Rose, Stuart (2), Jan. 20, 1954, Jan. 29, 1954
  - Rosebery, Marguerite T. (1), Mar. 23, 1954
  - Ross, Michael L. (2), Dec. 29, 1959, Jan. 27, 1960
  - Ross, Stuart T. (1), Sept. 4, 1962
  - Rowland, Ronald H. (1), Jan. 2, 1961
  - Roy, Leonard C. (1), Nov. 9, 1953
  - Ruderman, B. H., to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (1), June 9, 1960
  - Russell, Dean (1), Jan. 5, 1955
  - Russell, Fred (1), July 8, 1961
  - Russleape, Mary E. (1), n.d.
  - Rutowski, Agatha (7), June 1, 1954, Jan, 18, 1955, Feb. 17, 1955, May 18, 1955, Aug. 19, 1955, Sept. 16, 1955, Oct. 1, 1958
  - Rutterer, A. J. (1), Aug. 10, 1959
  - Sabrey, John D., to Lee Keedick (1), Jan. 27, 1955
  - Safford, Evelyn (1), Jan. 18, 1959
  - Sanders, Charles J. (1), July 29, 1959
  - Sanborn, Herbert (1), Dec. 27, 1955
  - Sarvola, Reinio (1), May 6, 1956
  - Saunders, J. R. (1), Dec. 29, 1953
  - Saunders, Richard P. (1), May 11, 1956
  - Saunders, Wilbour E. (1), Jan. 14, 1955
  - Schell, John (1), Sept. 1, 1954
  - Schenk, Elizabeth (143), 1950-1960
    Dates of letters: Nov. 3, 1950, Nov. 10 1950, Dec. 16, 1950, Dec. 27, 1950, Jan. 16, 1951, Jan. 30, 1951, Feb. 1, 1951, Feb. 20, 1951, Mar. 5, 1951, Mar. 15, 1951, Apr. 9, 1951, June 14, 1951, July 9, 1951, July 17, 1951, Aug. 1, 1951, Aug. 10, 1951, Sept. 4, 1951, Sept. 19, 1951, Sept. 24, 1951, Oct. 3, 1951, Oct. 9, 1951, Oct. 16, 1951, Oct. 19, 1959, Nov. 13, 1951, Dec. 4, 1951, Jan. 8, 1952, Jan. 12, 1952, Feb. 27, 1952, Mar. 28, 1952, May 6, 1952, May 14, 1952, June 3, 1952, June 9, 1952, June 13, 1952, June 20, 1952, July 1, 1952, July 7, 1952, July 8, 1952, July 16, 1952, July 23, 1952, Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 11, 1952, Sept. 12, 1952, Sept. 22, 1952, Oct. 3, 1952, Oct. 15, 1952, Oct. 21, 1952, Nov. 10, 1952, Nov. 14, 1952, Nov. 19, 1952, Dec. 8, 1952, Apr. 25, 1955, Jan. 5, 1953, Jan. 13, 1953, Jan. 30, 1953, Feb. 7, 1953, Mar. 2, 1953, Mar. 24, 1951, Apr. 17, 1953, May 20, 1953, May 25, 1953, June 19, 1953, June 23, 1953, June 26, 1953, July 2, 1953, Sept. 28, 1953, Oct. 2, 1953, Oct. 26, 1953, Dec. 23, 1953, Dec. 28, 1953, Jan. 19, 1954, Mar. 5, 1954, Apr. 1, 1954, May 4, 1954, May 26, 1954, May 28, 1954, June 2, 1954, July 6, 1954, July 13, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 16, 1954, Aug. 31, 1954, Sept. 16, 1954, Nov. 24, 1943, Dec. 1, 1954, Dec. 28, 1954, Dec. 31, 1954, Jan. 13, 1955, Jan. 14, 1955, Feb. 21, 1955, Mar. 8, 1955, May 19, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955, Sept. 7, 1955, Oct. 17, 1955, Oct. 27, 1955, Nov. 8, 1955, Nov. 22, 1955, Dec. 2, 1955, Feb. 17, 1956, Mar. 23, 1956, Apr. 26, 1956, Oct. 24, 1956, June 1, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956, Sept. 4, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, Nov, 27, 1956, Dec. 3, 1956, Dec. 13, 1956, Dec. 17, 1956, Jan. 5, 1957, Jan. 23, 1957, Feb. 15, 1957, Feb. 18, 1957, Apr. 1, 1957, June 6, 1957, June 14, 1957, July 30, 1957, Aug. 20, 1957, Nov. 9, 1957, Dec. 18, 1957, Feb. 13, 1958, Oct. 23, 1958, Nov. 22, 1958, Feb. 18, 1959, Mar. 12, 1959, Apr. 7, 1959, May 19, 1959, June 11, 1959, June 15, 1959, Sept.22, 1959, Oct. 14, 1959, Oct. 20, 1959, Nov. 20, 1959, Mar. 30, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept 29, 1960, Nov. 11, 1960, Nov. 18, 1960, Dec. 19, 1960, n.d.
  - Schmidt, Charles (1), n.d.
  - Schultz, Connie J. (1), Jan. 12, 1961
  - Schultz, Russell H. (1), Apr. 27, 1963
  - Scott, Glenn (1), Jan. 15, 1953
  - Scott, Otho E. (1), Feb. 19, 1957
  - Shackford, R. H. (1), Feb. 2, 1957
  - Shai, Lai (1), Sept. 28, 1956
  - Shain, Charles J. (4), Apr. 2, 1955, Apr. 21, 1955, May 30, 1955, n.d.
  - Shan, Trevor R. (1), Oct. 23, 1957
  - Shea, William (1), Sept. 16, 1955
  - Shemanski, Frances (2), Jan. 12, 1961, Jan. 2, 1962
  - Shen, Samson C. (7), Feb. 27, 1956, Apr. 2, 1956, Apr. 28, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Dec. 4, 1956, Apr. 4, 1958
  - Shen, T. H., to C. C. Shao (1), n.d.
  - Sherako, Lorraine (1), Dec. 8, 1959
  - Shideler, Jack (2), July 2, 1959, Oct. 12, 1959
  - Shih, Hu, to Magnus I. Gregerson (1), Mar. 16, 1956
  - Shin, Nichol (2), Nov. 26, 1954, Jan. 13, 1955
  - Shi Tae, Kim (1), Oct. 20, 1954
  - Shoemaker, Evelyn (1), March 25, 1956
  - Shouse, Len, to Lee Keedick (1), Dec. 27, 1954
  - Shriver, Thomas A. (1), Oct. 6, 1950
  - Shu, F. M. S. (2), Dec. 22, 1956, Jan. 28, 1957
  - Simester, Ralph E. (1), Nov. 8, 1952
  - Simmonds, Niva (2), Nov. 4, 1959, n.d.
  - Sinclair, John T. (3), Feb. 24, 1953, Aug. 11, 1964, n.d.
  - Sindelar, J. C. (6), July 28, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954, Sept. 2, 1954, Sept. 14, 1954, Oct. 6, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954
  - Skinner, Clara (3), Mar. 23, 1956, Aug, 6, 1956, Mar. 29, 1966
  - Skinner, L. E. (2), Jan. 17, 1957, Dec. 26, 1957
  - Skinner, Marguerite (1), n.d.
  - Sloane, Rubert D. (1), June 11, 1962
  - Smart, Alberto (1), Jan. 20, 1961
  - Smith, Anne E. (1), Feb. 17, 1954
  - Smith, Beatrice M. (1), May 14, 1953
  - Smith, C. R. (1), Dec. 29, 1953
  - Smith, Carolyn S. (1), n.d.
  - Smith, Frank L. (1), Jan. 13, 1959
  - Smith, Guy, L. (1), Oct. 6, 1952
  - Smith, Henry W. (1), Jan. 29, 1958
  - Smith, Paul C,, to Robert Keedick (1), June 23, 1955
  - Smith, Winfred R. (1), n.d.
  - Sneider, Vern (1), Feb. 18, 1955
  - Snell, Lottie (2), Feb. 20, 1958
  - Snell, Ray (3), Dec. 16, 1952, Aug. 5, 1953, Nov. 24, 1953
  - Soenksen, Rodney M. (1), Feb. 26, 1960
  - Solt, Guy, W., to H, W. Luhnow (1), Feb. 20, 1953
  - Soto, Teresa (1), June 27, 1955
  - Souder, M. Attie (2), Oct. 16, 1958, Nov. 9, 1958
  - Southgate, Herbert S. (3), July 15, 1953, Jan. 29, 1954, Sept. 4, 1954
  - Sowell, F. C. (1), June 20, 1951
  - Spadea Columns, Inc. (16), Sept. 30, 1957, May 26, 1958, Oct. 29, 1958, Nov. 28, 1958, Feb. 2, 1959, Mar. 4, 1959, Apr. 3, 1959, May 8, 1959, July 8, 1959, Sept. 11, 1959, Oct. 30, 1959, June 20, 1960, Sept. 28, 1960, Nov. 14, 1960, n.d., n.d.
  - Spadea, James V., to Frank Dorn and Bill Reiche (2), July 29, 1953, Oct. 15, 1953
  - Spadea, James V. (44), 1953-1960
    Dates of letters: July 21, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Aug. 10, 1953, Oct. 8, 1953, Oct. 19, 1953, Nov. 6, 1953, Nov. 9, 1953, Nov. 10, 1953, Nov. 10, 1953, Nov. 13, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953, Dec. 2, 1953, Jan. 5, 1954, Jan. 6, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Jan. 28, 1954, Mar. 2, 1954, Mar. 9, 1954, June 24, 1954, July 30, 1954, Sept. 16, 1954, Oct. 1, 1954, Oct. 5, 1954, Dec. 1, 1954, Dec. 30, 1954, Jan. 19, 1955, Apr. 11, 1955, June 22, 1955, Setp. 29, 1955, Oct. 4, 1955, Dec. 8, 1955, Jan. 4, 1956, Jan. 19, 1956, Feb. 20, 1956, Feb. 20, 1956, Aug. 1, 1956, Oct. 23, 1956, Nov. 27, 1956, Apr. 10, 1958, Jan. 16, 1959, Oct. 12, 1960, n.d., n.d.
  - Spadea, Stirling (10), Nov. 9, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, May 24, 1954, Dec. 7, 1956, Jan. 4, 1957, May 20, 1957, July 18, 1957, Aug. 26, 1957, Aug. 26, 1958, May 1, 1959
  - Sparks, Fred (1), Mar. 20, 1955
  - Speer, Robert P. (1), Aug. 5, 1955
  - Speers, Theodore C. (1), Mar. 9, 1951
  - Spencer, George A. P., to E. Bigwood (1), Sept. 14, 1960
  - Spender, Percy, to U. G. Murphy (1), Jan. 4, 1957
  - Spottswood, C. L. (1), Mar. 23, 1956
  - Stahlman, James G. (1), Aug. 27, 1951
  - Stanley, H. F. (4), June 24, 1959, July 9, 1959, Sept. 28, 1959, Oct. 12, 1959
  - Starbuck, Philip N. (4), Aug. 22, 1951, Sept. 7, 1951, Aug. 27, 1952, Sept. 5, 1952
  - Starr, C. C. (2), Mar. 15, 1957, n.d.
  - Steeves, John M. (1), Dec. 28, 1965
  - Steiner, Anthony (1), Apr. 26, 1963
  - Sterling, Phyllis M. (1), Oct. 24, 1952
  - Stewart, James L. (2), Oct. 28, 1948, Oct. 5, 1956
  - Stewart, Shan (6), Aug. 7, 1959, Feb. 18, 1960, Sept. 8, 1962, Oct. 3, 1962, Oct. 13, 1962, n.d.
  - Steyn, Mary T., to William J. Dowling and Mildred D. Glass (2), Jan. 24, 1957, Mar. 18, 1957
  - Stokeman, Christina (1), Oct. 29, 1953
  - Stand, Eleanor (2), Apr. 30, 1953, May 23, 1953
  - Straus, Roger W. (2), July 13, 1955, July 19, 1955
  - Straus, Ernest (5), July 29, 1952, June 8, 1953, June 9, 1953, Mar. 8, 1955, n.d.
  - Straus, Filicia B. (1), Dec. 2, 1953
  - Strube, William F., to Charles Elder, Stewart Kritsky, Bernie Schweid, Bruce Mills, Howard Clarke, and Henry Regnery (6), Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug 19, 1952, Oct. 7, 1954, Dec. 8, 1954, June 29, 1955
  - Strube, William F. (30), 1952-1959
    Dates of letters: May 8, 1952, May 14, 1952, May 19, 1952, June 16, 1952, June 25, 1952, Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug 25, 1952, Sept. 2, 1952, Sept. 9, 1952, Sept. 19, 1952, Sept. 24, 1952, Oct. 3, 1952, Oct. 7, 1952, Dec. 8, 1952, Jan. 9, 1953, Apr. 22, 1953, June 10, 1953, June 11, 1953, June 17, 1953, Jan. 28, 1954, Sept. 10, 1954, Nov. 4, 1954, Feb. 14, 1955, Feb. 18, 1955, Mar. 7, 1955, June 30, 1955, Sept. 23, 1959, n.d., n.d.
  - Stryker, Lisie B. (1), Mar. 11, 1959
  - Stuntz, Hugh C.. (1), Sept. 19, 1952
  - Stutts, Barbara L. (1), n.d.
  - Suh, Eton (8), Nov. 17, 1950, Mar. 26, 1951, Apr. 3, 1951, Sept. 19, 1951, June 12, 1952, Nov. 20, 1953, Aug. 4, 1954, Aug. 29, 1954
  - Summers, Joe A. (1), Sept. 4, 1951
  - Sun, Lew Ho (1), June 20, 1952
  - Sutherland, Kirk E., to Lee Keedick (1), July 13, 1951
  - Swanson, Helen R. (1), Jan. 7, 1954
  - Tanner, E. S. (1), Sept. 6, 1952
    9
  - Tao, Frank (4), Aug. 29, 1955, Jan. 6, 1959, July 30, 1959, Nov. 28, 1959
  - Tate, Velma N. (4), May 22, 1957, Aug. 16, 1957, Sept. 16, 1957, June 3, 1958
  - Tanabe, Shinichi (1), Dec. 26, 1957
  - Tay, Paul (5), Dec. 4*1956, Mar. 20, 1959, May 18, 1959, May 28, 1959, Aug. 22, 1959
  - Tayl, Jim (1), Sept. 23, 1957
  - Teetor, Paul (2), Mar. 14, 1951, May 18, 1951
  - Templeton, Payne (1), Dec. 28, 1956
  - Tenske, Marcia (1), n.d.
  - Thacher, Liz (1), Mar. 19, 1951
  - Thaller, Victor C. (1), June 7, 1961
  - Theoblad, Jack W. (1), June 1, 1955
  - Thompson, Curtis C., to Mituko (3), June 13, 1950, Sept. 26, 1950, Nov, 22, 1950
  - Thompson, Naomi (1), Jan. 29, 1957
  - Thompson, P. W. (1), Nov. 24, 1958
  - Thompson, Jill (1), Nov. 30, 1964
  - Thompson, Marcelline E. (1), Feb. 10, 1966
  - Thomson, Robert P. (1), June 14, 1957
  - Thurman, Pauline (1), Mar. 5, 1962
  - Tiffany, Helen (1), Feb. 19, 1955
  - Todd, Jo Ann (1), May 26, 1960
  - Tomkins, Ellsworth, to Richard Walsh (1), Jan. 5, 1956
  - Tomkins, Ellsworth (1), Dec. 6, 1955
  - Tones, V. E. (1), Sept. 28, 1957
  - Tong, H. K. (3), May 28, 1956, May 29, 1956, Feb. 6, 1958
  - Tower, Howard E. (1), Apr. 20, 1959
  - Tracy, Crete C. (2), Feb. 1, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957
  - Tracey, Jean (1), Feb. 8, 1955
  - Treadwell, James H. W. (2), Sept. 22, 1962, Oct. 17, 1962
  - Traum, William R. (2), Mar. 22, 1952, Nov. 26, 1952
  - Truitt, Patricia (1), July 30, 1957
  - Tseng, George (1), Jan. 12, 1958
  - Tsiang, Tingfu F. (2), Nov. 24, 1954, Feb. 23, 1955
  - Tuerk, Gladys R. (1), Jan. 13, 1959
  - Tull, James N. (1), May 29, 1956
  - Tunney, Gene (1), Dec. 11, 1956
  - Turnbull, Ruth W. (1), July 13, 1955
  - Turner, George, to Deryck Aluvihare, S. N. Chib, M. B. K. Malik, and Sri Budojo (4), Sept. 28, 1959
  - Turner, George (2), May 22, 1958, Mar. 11, 1959
  - Turner, Lucille C. (1), Nov. 18, 1958
  - Turner, William D. (1), Jan. 14, 1955
  - Tyler, Lee (3), Apr. 1, 1959, Aug. 11, 1959, Aug. 26, 1959
  - Ulrich, Jolton, to Dr. Poling (1), n.d.
  - Underwood, G. (1), May 25, 1962
  - Ushida, Hirozo (2), Oct. 7, 1959, Jan. 28, 1960
  - Utley, William T. (1), Nov. 11, 1959
  - Vander Meer, Alma (1), Sept. 4, 1956
  - Vance, R. R., to R. H. Porter (1), n.d.
  - Vance, R. R. (1), Aug. 31, 1955
  - Vandas, Edna (1), July 10, 1953
  - Van Ness, Catherine L. (1), Feb. 10, 1958
  - Vaurs, Roger (1), Jan. 22, 1958
  - Veigel, Ernest W. (1), May 5, 1959
  - Viteri, Luis (1), Mar. 7, 1961
  - Vogel, Frank J. (2), Apr. 5, 1960, Apr. 18, 1960
  - Vogt, Gertrude E. (2), May 5, 1954, May 13, 1954
  - Voorhess, Lacy (1), n.d.
  - Waldhorn, Valerie, to Barbara Beggi (1), July 8, 1963
  - Waldhorn, Valerie (2), June 17, 1963, Aug. 3, 1965
  - Waldorf, Howard (3), Feb. 8, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, June 10, 1959
  - Walker, Richard. (1), Feb. 6, 1959
  - Wallace, DeWitt, to Lim Rei Cheng (1), May 19, 1958
  - Wallace, DeWitt (5), July 18, 1956, Sept. 10, 1956, Nov. 20, 1956, July 15, 1957
  - Wallace, G. D., to H. Johnson (1), July 9, 1963
  - Wallin, Katherine, to Robert Keedick (1), Nov. 13, 1957
  - Walsh, Agatha, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr. (1), July 1, 1959
  - Walsh, Mary 0. L. (93), 1957-1965
    Dates of letters: Nov. 11, 1957, Mar. 21, 1958, Mar. 26, 1958, June 3, 1958, Aug. 6, 1958, Aug. 15, 1958, Aug. 27, 1958, Feb.3, 1959, Feb. 11, 1959, Feb. 18, 1959, Feb. 18, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, Mar. 6, 1959, Apr. 7, 1959, Apr. 29, 1959, July 21, 1959, Oct. 2, 1959, Dec. 10, 1959, Jan. 29, 1960, Jan. 22, 1960, Mar. 29, 1960, Apr. 28, 1960, May 4, 1960, May 18, 1960, June 8, 1960, June 14, 1960, June 30, 1960, July 18, 1960, July 19, 1960, Aug. 3, 1960, Aug. 4, 1960, Aug. 18, v 1960, Sept. 12, 1960, Sept. 14, 1960, Nov. 2, 1960, Jan. 9. 1961, Jan. 24, 1961, Mar. 23, 1961, Apr. 5, 1961, Apr. 14, 1961, Apr.. 14, 1961, Apr. 24, 1961, Sept. 11, 1961, Sept. 26, 1961, Oct. 27, 1961, Nov. 3, 1961, Nov. 8, 1961, Nov. 17, 1961, Dec. 28.,' 1961, Jan. 8, 1962, Mar. 13, 1962, Apr. 25, 1962, Sept. 10, 1962, Oct. 18, 1962, Dec. 6, 1962, Jan. 3, 1963, Jan. 22, 1963, Jan. 29, 1963, Feb. 6, 1963, Feb. 7, 1963, Feb. 13, 1962, May 10, 1963, May 21, 1963, June 10, 1963, June 26, 1963, July 3, 1963, July 10, 1963, Aug. 2, 1963, Aug. 15, 1963, Aug. 27, 1963, Aug. 27, 1963, Oct. 2, 1963, Nov. 6, 1963, Nov. 13, 1963, Nov. 14, 1963, Nov. 27, 1963, Dec. 11, 1963, Dec. 12, 1963, Apr. 29, 1964, May 14, 1964, June 26, 1964, July 16, 1964, July 29, 1964, Sept. 3, 1964, Sept. 11, 1964, Oct. 21, 1964, Nov. 11, 1964, Dec. 11, 1964, May 22, 1965, Sept. 14, 1965, Spet. 22, 1965, Oct. 26, 1965, Oct. 26, 1965
  - Walsh, Richard J. to Daniel A. Poling, John F. Cronin, Dave Schaffnit, J. Calvitt Clarke, Marvin Liebman, Raymond E. Fideler, Robert T. Oliver, I. Yokota, Peter Hiatt, Virginia Kirkus, Norman E., Koehler, Shirley Fockler, Robert Arculli, and Richard R. Saunders (15), Nov. 25, 1955, Jan. 6, 1956, July 30, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956, Jan. 29, 1957, Jan. 8, 1959, Feb. 24, 1959, Mar. 17, 1959, July 31, 1959, Sept. 3, 1959, May 26, 1960, Nov. 9, 1960, June 23, 1960, Dec. 21, 1960, May 12, 1961
  - Walsh, Richard J. (396), 1955-1965
    Dates of letters: Apr. 22, 1955, May 13, 1955, May 26, 1955, June 1, 1955, June 15, 1955, July 8, 1955, July 13, 1955, July 14, 1955, July 20, 1955, July 20, 1955, Aug. 16, 1955, Aug. 23, 1955, Aug. 26, 1955, Sept. 8, 1955, Sept. 20, 1955, Oct. 7, 1955, Oct. 11, 1955, Oct. 12, 1955, Oct. 12, 1955, Oct. 27, 1955, Oct. 31, 1955, Nov. 15, 1955, Nov. 17, 1955, Dec. 5, 1955, Jan. 6, 1956, Jan. 20, 1956, Feb. 6, 1956, Feb. 21, 1956, Mar. 2, 1956, Mar. 7, 1956, Mar. 8, 1956, Mar. 22, 1956, Mar. 27, 1956, Apr. 4, 1956, Apr. 12, 1956, Apr. 18, 1956, Apr. 26, 1956, May 21, 1956, May 28, 1956, June 1, 1956, June 22, 1956, July 2, 1956, July 18, 1956, Aug. 3, 1956 July 30, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Aug. 16, 1956, Aug. 21, 1956, Aug. 27, 1956, Aug. 27, 1956, Sept. 12, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956, Oct. 9, 1956, Oct. 15, 1956, Oct. 22, 1956, Oct. 29, 1956, Nov. 13, 1956, Nov. 15, 1956, Nov. 21, 1956, Nov. 27, 1956, Dee. 5, 1956, Dee. 7, 1956, Dee. 14, 1956, Dee. 21, 1956, Dee. 28, 1956, Jan. 9, 1957, Jan. 23, 1957, Jan. 29, 1957, Feb. 1, 1957, Feb. 11, 1957, Feb. 14, 1957, Mar. 8, 1957, Mar. 14, 1957, Mar. 22, 1957, Mar. 27, 1957, Apr. 2, 1957, Apr. 5, 1957, Apr. 12, 1957, Apr, 24, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 3, 1957, May 10, 1957, May 14, 1957, May 28, 1957, June 24, 1957, August 22, 1957, Oct. 18, 1957, Nov. 8, 1957, Nov. 11, 1957, Nov. 13, 1957, Nov. 15, 1957, Nov. 22, 1957, Nov. 26, 1957, Dee. 5, 1957, Dee. 13, 1957, Dee. 18, 1957, Feb. 10, 1958, Feb. 20, 1958, Feb. 25, 1958, Mar. 13, 1958, Apr. 7, 1958, Apr. 14, 1958, Apr. 16, 1958, Apr. 17, 1958, May 8, 1958, May 19, 1958, May 21, 1958, June 20, 1958, June 27, 1958, July 21, 1958, July 30, 1958, Aug. 26, 1958, Sept. 11, 1958, Sept. 23, 1958, Oct. 23, 1958, Oct. 27, 1958, Nov. 5, 1958, Nov. 10, 1958, Nov. 11, 1958, Nov. 18, 1958,- Nov. 18, 1958, Nov. 20, 1958, Nov. 21, 1958, Dee. 3, 1958, Dee. 5, 1958, Dee. 8, 1958, Dee. 18, 1958, Dee. 30, 1958, Jan. 9, 1959, Jan. 12, 1959, Jan. 16, 1959, Jan. 22, 1959, Feb. 10, 1959, Feb. 16, 1959, Feb. 17, 1959, Feb. 20, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, Mar. 10, 1959, Mar. 11, 1959, Mar. 20, 1959, Mar. 20, 1959, Mar. 26, 1959, Mar. 27, 1959, Apr. 2, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 21, 1959, Apr. 29, 1959, May 4, 1959, May 14, 1959, May 18, 1959, May 25, 1959, June 1, 1959, June 16, 1959, June 19, 1959, June 24, 1959, July 15, 1959, July 20, 1959, July 21, 1959, July 24, 1959, July 30, 1959, Aug. 4, 1959, Aug. 18,1959 Aug. 24, 1959, Aug. 28, 1959, Sept. 3, 1959, Sept. 22, 1959, Sept. 28, 1959, Sept. 30, 1959, Oct. 5, 1959, Oct. 9, 1959, Oct. 14, 1959, Oct. 21, 1959, Nov. 10, 1959, Oct. 26, 1959, Oct. 29, 1959, Nov. 17, 1959, Nov. 23, 1959, Dee. 7, 1959, Dee. 29, 1959, Jan. 22, 1960, Jan. 25, 1960, Feb. 2, I960, Feb. 4, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 19, 1960, Feb. 24, 1960, Feb. 26, 1960, Mar. 3, 1960, Mar. 8, 1960, Mar. 8, 1960, Mar. 10, 1960, Mar. 21, 1960, Mar. 24, 1960, Apr. 1, 1960, Apr. 20, 1960, Apr. 21, 1960, May 4, 1960; 9 May 4, 1960, May 12, 1960, May 24, 1960, June 10, 1960, June 13, 1960, June 15, 1960, June 27, 1960, June 29, 1960, June 29, 1960, June 29, 1960, July 8, 1960, July 12, 1960, July 12, 1960, July 18, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 26, 1960, July 27, 1960, July 29, 1960, Aug. 11, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960, Aug. 15, 1960, Aug. 17, 1960, Aug. 18, 1960, Aug. 23, 1960, Aug. 24, 1960, Aug. 24, 1960, Aug. 30, 1960, Sept. 6, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept. 13, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 9, 1960, Nov. 10, 1960, Nov. 15, 1960, Nov. 16, 1960, Dec. 5, 1960, Dec. 9, 1960, Jan. 3, 1951, Jan. 5, 1961, Jan. 13, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 30 1961, Feb. 10, 1961, Feb. 15, 1961, Feb. 17, 1961, Feb. 23, 1961, Feb. 23, 1961, Feb. 24, 1961, Mar. 2, 1961, Mar. 8, 1961, Mar. 27, 1961, Apr. 3, 1961, Apr. 10, 1961, Apr. 11, 1961, Apr. 19, 1961, Apr. 21, 1961, Apr. 26, 1961, Apr. 26, 1961, May.8, 1961, May 31, 1961, June 2, 1961, June 8, 1961, June 8, 1961, June 20, 1961, June 20, 1961, June 23, 1961, June 30, 1961, July 12, 1961, July 25, 1961, July 25, 1961, Aug. I, 1961, Aug. 11, 1961, Aug. 24, 1961, Sept. 8, 1961, Sept. 13, 1961, Sept. 14, 1961, Sept. 29, 1961, Sept. 29, 1961, Oct. 3, 1961, Oct. 6, 1961, Oct. 23, 1961, Dec. 1, 1961, Dec. 4, 1961, Dec. 11, 1961, Dec. 13, 1961, Dec. 28, 1961, Jan. 3, 1962, Jan. 5, 1962, Jan. II, 1962, Jan. 15, 1962, Jan. 17, 1962, Jan. 19, 1962, Jan. 23, 1962, Feb. 5, 1962, Feb. 16, 1962, Feb. 21, 1962, Feb. 28, 1962, Apr. 30, 1962, May 2, 1962, June 20, 1962, June 22, 1962, Aug. 27, 1962, Sept. 27, 1962, Oct. 12, 1962, Nov. 9, 1962, Nov. 13, 1962, Nov. 27, 1962, Dec. 3, 1962, Jan. 2, 1963, Jan. 3, 1963, Jan. 25, 1963, Feb. 12, 1963, Feb. 15-, 1963, Feb. 19, 1963, Feb. 19, 1963, Mar. 1, 1963, Mar. 5, 1963, Mar. 19, 1963, May 10, 1963, June 5, 1963, June 10, 1963, June 17, 1963, July 3, 1963, Aug. 5, 1963, Sept. 3, 1963, Sept. 6, 1963, Sept. 10, 1963, Oct. 1, 1963, Oct. 14, 1963, Oct. 25, 1963, Dec. 4, 1963, Dec. 12, 1963, Dec. 19, 1963, Dec. 24, 1963, Jan. 6, 1964, Feb. 10, 1964, Mar. 18., 1964, Mar. 27, 1964, Apr. 13, 1964, June 3, 1964, July 8, 1964, July 8, 1964, Aug. 25, 1964, Sept. 9, 1964, Sept. 23, 1964, Oct. 6, 1964, Oct. 9, 1964, Dec. 30, 1964, Feb. 3, 1965, Feb. 12, 1965, Feb. 20, 1965, Mar. 5, 1965, Apr, 6, 1965, Apr. 27, 1965, May 6, 1965, May 14, 1965, June 11, 1965, June 18, 1965, June 30, 1965, July 13, 1965, July 19, 1965, July 22, 1965, July 23, 1965, July 27, 1965, Aug. 3, 1965, Aug. 6, 1965, Aug. 9, 1965, Aug. 18, 1965, Aug. 24, 1965, Aug. 27, 1965, Aug. 27, 1965, Sept. 14, 1965, Sept. 16. 1965, Sept. 21, 1965, Oct. 28, 1965, Nov. 2, 1965, Nov. 19, 1965, Nov. 22, 1965, Nov. 29, 1965, Dec. 6, 1965, Dec. 9, 1965, Dec. 10, 1965, Dec. 14, 1965, n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d.
    10
  - Walter, Francis E. (1), June 28, 1956
  - Ward, Hiley H. (25), 1956-1958
    Dates of letters: Feb. 7, 1956, Feb. 15, 1956, Feb. 22, 1956, Feb. 28, 1956, Mar. 5, 1956, Mar. 15, 1956, Mar. 21, 1956, Mar. 29, 1956, Apr. 12, 1956, Apr. 19, 1956, May 4, 1956, May 28, 1956, May 31, 1956, June 4, 1956, June 6, 1956, July 2, 1956, July 30, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Sept. 21, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Nov. 15, 1956, Dec. 11, 1956, Nov. 4, 1957, Apr. 10, 1958
  - Warfield, Charles H. (1), Feb. 18, 1954
  - Washko, Michael (1), Dec. 19, 1957
  - Watson, Tom (4), June 28, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953, n.d.
  - Wayman, Paul L, to Mr. Holladay (1), Sept. 5, 1960
  - Webb, Elaine (1), n.d.
  - Weems, Clarence N. (1), Oct. 26. 1952
  - Wei, C. C. (3), Feb. 19, 1957, Feb. 19, 1958, Apr. 16, 1958
  - Whalen, Richard (1), Aug. 12, 1956
  - Wheatley, Ralph (1), June 25, 1954
  - Wheeler, W. L. (1), June 16, 1953
  - White, Robert L. (2), July 30, 1958, n.d.
  - White, Sue T. (5), Nov. 26, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958, Dec. 13, 1959, Aug. 20, 1960, n.d.
  - White, William L., to Alfred S. Dasheil (1), Aug. 9, 1954
  - White, William L. (11), Mar. 4, 1954, June 24, 1954, Aug. 5, 1954, Aug. 6, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 12, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954, Oct. 6, 1954, Feb. 2, 1955, n.d.
  - Whitla, J. M. (1), Dec. 28, 1964
  - Whitman, E. S., to Alice Widener (1), Dec. 10, 1956
  - Whitted, G. W., to Richard J. Walsh (1), July 2, 1959
  - Widener, Alice (20), 1955-1958